DON OMONDI ONYANGO

Cinematographer & Graphics Designer

Experience: 3 years | Available: Immediately | Location: Nairobi onyangodonomondi@gmail.com | +254741590670 || 0748453590

ABOUT ME

I'm a qualified graphic design specialist. Over three years ago, I started working as a graphic designer. I have therefore acquired all the creative skills necessary to produce a visual concept that unquestionably serves as a channel of communication with customers, clients, sponsors, etc.

WORK EXPERIENCE

K24 TELEVISION

Graduate Attaché | Television production

Nairobi, Kenya

2020-09-01 | 2020-11-01

Handling Pre-Production, Production and Post Production assignment as guided by the supervisor.

DEKILA LIMITED

Graphics designer Nairobi, Kenya

2021-08-01 | present

Designing vectors and illustrations for T-shirt printing, Printing using large formats, plotter and DTFs, designing banners, flyers and Posters for company clients, maintaining online social media presence and updating the company website.

ZION PEARL PUBLISHER

Graphics designer | Senior

Nairobi, Kenya

2021-08-01 | 2021-012-01

Part time designing and developing books designs for publishing, editing magazines and producing marketing materials.

EDUCATION:

MOI UNIVERSITY

Bachelor of Arts Degree in Film & Media Studies

ORIWO BOYS HIGH SCHOOL

KCSE CERTFICATE B 63 POINTS

OBER BOYS' PRIMARY

KCPE CERTFICATE 370 MARKS

SKILLS

- Photography
- Video Editing Using Adobe Premier Pro CC and AE.
- Image manipulation using Photoshop CC and Adobe Illustrator.
- Publishing using Adobe InDesign.
- Social media management

GRAPHICS DESIGN PORTFOLIO BIN

 https://drive.google.com/folderview?id=14opd1QS1gQqwcTKqVUyilDMHEKpT7K-1 https://drive.google.com/folderview?id=1HbBZpMh1vf7d2kXAVkMvCK-B5wwaaVZg

REFEREES

Mr. Bii CosmasLecturer Moi University,

Tel: 0721485349

Mr. Derick Kithela CEO DEKILA LTD, Tel: 0712095724